Guide to the NAMBLA manuscripts, circa 1960-1990.
NAMBLA manuscripts
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
NAMBLA manuscripts, circa 1960-1990.
7729
North American Man/Boy Love Association.
0.1 cubic feet.
Manuscripts, Printed Materials, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Manuscripts submitted for publication to the North American Man-Boy Love Association, together with copies of NAMBLA's constitution. Included are short stories, poetry, and essays.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Manuscripts submitted for publication to the North American Man-Boy Love Association, together with copies of NAMBLA's constitution. Included are short stories, poetry, and essays.
SUBJECTS
Names:
North American Man/Boy Love Association.
Subjects:
Pedophilia.; Pedophilia--Fiction.; Sodomy.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting program: Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. NAMBLA Journals, Papers, and Related Materials
  - Towards a Dialog: "Papers Presented by the North American Man Boy Love Association at the Boston University School of Nursing Conference on 'Child Victimazation'," March 1981. New York: NAMBLA, 1981. 4to, pictorial wrappers, 16 pages. First edition. (Box 1)
  - Thorstad, David. "Man/Boy Love and Feminism." N.p. [probably New York]: 1980. 4to, stapled sheets, 5 pages. First edition of this "paper ... drafted by David Thorstad as a contribution to a discussion within the North American Man/Boy Love Association." (Box 1)
  - Angel Talk, Number 1 (July 1989). Oradell, New Jersey: Angel Talk, 1989. First issue of this boy-love periodical, very scarce. (Box 1)
- Series II. Leaflets and Flyers published by NAMBLA in New York and Los Angeles
  - "Introducing the North American Man/Boy Love Association." Single sheet folded to make 12 pages, illustrated., 1982 (Box 1)
  - "Introduction to the North American Man/Boy Love Association With Special Information on the Los Angeles Chapter." Single sheet folded to make 6pages., early 1980s (Box 1)
  - "NAMBLA-Los Angeles." Small broadside, card stock., early 1980s (Box 1)
  - "NAMBLA is an Activist Organization." Small broadside, card stock., early 1980s (Box 1)
  - "Draft Constitution for the North American Man/Boy Love Association." 4to, stapled sheets, 4 pages., early 1980s (Box 1)
  - The Constitution of the North American Man/Boy Love Association. [New York]: 1983. 4to, single sheet printed on both sides. (Box 1)
  - "Boy-Lovers Crash Conference Aimed at Man-Boy Sex." Single Sheet. Press Release., early 1980s (Box 1)
  - "Who Is This LAPD Detective Lloyd Martin Whom B.U. Honors Tonight?" Legal-size sheet printed on both sides., 1981 (Box 1)
  - "Dear Friend, Thank You For Writing Us." Single Sheet, illustrated., early 1980s (Box 1)
  - "NAMBLA...Introduction." Legal-size sheet, illustrated., early 1980s (Box 1)
  - "All Sex is Not Rape." Single sheet, illustrated., early 1980s (Box 1)
  - "Fight State Molestation!" Single sheet, illustrated., early 1980s (Box 1)
  - "Dear Sir:I am a Fourteen Year Old Boy Involved Sexually With An Older Guy I happen to Love Very Much." Two stapled sheets, 4 pages., early 1980s (Box 1)
  - "An Injury to One is An Injury to All!" Single 4to sheet, illustrated., early 1980s (Box 1)
  - "Statement by the North American Man/Boy Love Association/ New York City Lesbian and Gay Pride March, June 29, 1980." 4to, single sheet, illustrated by Sydney Smith., early 1980s (Box 1)
  - "Love Is Not A Crime." 4to, single sheet, illustrated by Sydney Smith., early 1980s (Box 1)